♪♪
Good night.
We need volume. Some for growth.
I'll do my best.
I've been working on my reutering, and if I get back earlier than yesterday, I'll be able to see the camp.
And I like it that way, too.
I like that. I like her ionic cuteness. I like that she's so used to it.
And, ah, welcome to stop today.
I'm Mike. Nice to meet you.
Nice!
Can I have some?
Our joint declaration of war.
It's already been two years.
It's already been two years. Did we become big sisters with the arrival of the picture mayonnaise already?
Have we become older sisters?
Hang on, hang on, hang on.
Shall I put this down? No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Stop it.
You know, there are a lot of people who like the relationship between Cocoyamama and Auger.
That's true. It's different from mayonnaise.
It's a personality bomb.
Tsun tsun tsun.
They are bombs of individuality, and they respect each other.
They respect each other.
It's a good relationship.
They fight each other.
But I think it's a good fight.
It's good. You can get more excitement from the top.
But you don't see it. That's the point.
Something's being filmed.
There.
Where am I?
Love round!
B.I.N.A.
EBITCHU
Mikuyoke
Miko
EBICHU
Fight!
Let's look for them again today.
She always turns her ponytail.
I was sure he'd do it again today.
That's why I was singing like this.
But he still grabbed it.
Amazing.
That's amazing.
Yuna has a habit of holding people's hair.
When I was in there before, I saw Mirei's rixtape.
Yeah.
She kept holding her hair and putting it on her phone case.
Look, it's Mirei's hair.
And after that, she put it in the pudding case.
She put it in the pudding case at least once.
Isn't that crazy?
We did the spring tour together last year.
This year, this year...
My mom kind of told me to throw it out.
She told me to throw it away.
I mean, we're lucky to have found each other.
And more than that it's just an endearment
So we can hang on just a little bit longer
Let's say that one word together
I'm not ashamed to say it
I'd rather say it
I love you.
Thank you very much.
End.
I can't believe we're here for the third year too!
I'll do my best!
Yay!
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah
See you soon.